Anooj Vadodkar

A UC Merced undergraduate student pursuing a Bachelors of Science in Computer Science and Engineering, with experience across a variety of languages and engines. Founding officer and current President of the UC Merced Game Development Club, working with the University and other organizations to bring game development knowledge to students.

408-768-6886 anoojrv@gmail.com anooj.xyz https://www.linkedin.com/in/an oojvadodkar/

EDUCATION

University of California At Merced

Bachelors of Science in Computer Science and Engineering August 2018 - Present. GPA: 3.7/4.0

Relevant Coursework: Intro to Object Oriented Programming, Database Systems, Linear Algebra and Differential Equations, Technical Writing.

Awards: Dean's Honors List for Academic Year 2019. Chancellor's Honors List for Academic Year 2020-2021.

EXPERIENCE

Student Game Developers AllianceWebmaster

September 2020 - Present

Currently maintaining and updating the website for the Student Game Developers Alliance, or SGDA, namely responsible for making additions and servicing the website to include information about seasonal events such as the SGDA Summit and Game Jam.

University of California, Merced, Bright Success Center Sophomore Success Intern

November 2019 - April 2020

Developed and implemented a data strategy to analyze Sophomore success and retention at UC Merced, as well as the existing programs on campus that support them. Provided a recommendation list on how to best assist Sophomore students in their university journey.

PROJECTS

Bonds of Yggdrasil

Self Developed

Developed a 2D Adventure game in the Godot engine solo, using assets from opengameart.org and itch.io. Worked on game programming, writing, and game design. Submitted to the SGDA 2020 Summer Jam.

SKILLS

Database Systems.

Game Development.

Unity and Unreal.

Object Oriented Programming.

LANGUAGES

C++ - Advanced

Java - Advanced

SQL - Advanced

Python - Experienced

C# - Experienced

ORGANIZATIONS

UC Merced Game Development Club - President

Student Game Developers Alliance - Webmaster

Association for Computing Machinery - Member